parkcitymountain.com 2013-05-14

# Privacy

Effective date: January 20, 2012

## Our Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our electronic information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and we will update it immediately if our policies change.

## The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to information you supply to Park City Mountain Resort. The information may be provided via the Resort's websites or at various other locations including points of sale at the Resort. The types of personal information collected may include:  
Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
Credit/Debit Card Information  
(etc.)  
On some webpages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:  
Name  
Address  
Phone Number  
(etc.)

## The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order or in the course of business related to that transaction. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.  
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.  
We may offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift.  
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.  
You can sign up for our e-newsletter on our website if you would like to receive email updates from Park City Mountain Resort. Information you submit on other pages of our website will not be used for this purpose unless you agree to receive updates.  
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with sponsors. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose personally identifiable information.  
Park City Mountain Resort will never use, sell, rent or share the personally identifiable information provided to us to any third party for any reason, except for in certain special cases in which we may disclose your personally identifiable information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to you, or otherwise injuring or interfering with Park City Mountain Resort's rights, property or operations, other Park City Mountain Resort's site users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe the law requires it, or in response to any demand by law enforcement authorities in connection with a criminal investigation, or civil or administrative authorities in connection with a pending civil case, administrative investigation or investigation conducted by Park City Mountain Resort. We shall have no obligation to inform you of our compliance with the law, including without limitation a response to a law enforcement request or a valid subpoena.

## Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  
We encrypt the pipe through which personal information, such as credit card numbers, is sent, using the most up-to-date technology such as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to ensure that your information is safe as it is sent over the Internet to our server. While we strive to safeguard your personal information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

## Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.  This Site is for a general audience.  We ask that parents supervise their children while online.

## How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can request information about all your personally identifiable information that we maintain by contacting us at [privacy@pcski.com](mailto:privacy@pcski.com) or by sending postal mail to: Park City Mountain Resort Privacy Policy, PO Box 39, Park City, UT 84060. To protect your privacy and security we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.  
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a written request that credibly shows error.

## How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 435-649-8111, send us an email at [privacy@pcski.com](mailto:privacy@pcski.com) or you may contact us at: Park City Mountain Resort Privacy Policy, PO Box 39, Park City, UT 84060

## Privacy Policy Updates

We may update this privacy policy from time to time. When we do so, we will post the new privacy policy on this page and change the date at the top of the policy. Therefore, we encourage you to check the date of our privacy policy whenever you visit this Site for any updates or changes. If you have any questions about this privacy policy or have concerns that are not addressed here, please contact Park City Mountain Resort (see "How To Contact" Us above).

## Links

This site includes links to other websites. We provide these links as a courtesy to you and we do not have control over the operation of the websites, even though they may use the Park City Mountain Resort name or logo. In addition, you may sign up for accounts on some of these websites. These websites have their own privacy and information security policy and terms and conditions and do not necessarily follow our privacy policy. Their policies will control their collection and use of your personal information. Visitors should consult the other websites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. In addition, when you browse, they may place their own cookies on your computer and we do not control cookies placed on your computer by third parties whose sponsor links appear on our Site.  
The appearance of a link does not imply Park City Mountain Resort endorsement, nor is Park City Mountain Resort responsible for the contents of any linked site. You access them at your own risk.

## International Users

If you are located outside of the United States, please note that this Site is hosted on computer servers in the United States. Any personal information collected through this Site may be transferred to the United States and other countries that might not provide an equivalent level of protection as the data protection laws in your home country. Your use of this Site or submission of any personal information will therefore constitute your consent to the transfer of your personal information outside of your home country.

## Collection of Information

By providing personal information to Park City Mountain Resort you agree and consent that we may collect and use your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy.  
In addition, where appropriate, we may obtain specific authorizations or consents from time to time. For example, we may seek consent to use and share personal information after it has been collected in those cases where Park City Mountain Resort wishes to use the information for a purpose not previously identified or for which the individual concerned has not previously provided consent.  
In most cases, and subject to legal and contractual restrictions, an individual is free to refuse or withdraw his or her consent at any time upon reasonable, advance notice. It should be noted that in some circumstances, certain Park City Mountain Resort products and services can only be offered if a person provides personal information to Park City Mountain Resort. If you choose not provide us with any required personal information, we may not be able to offer the products or services requested. We will inform you of the consequences of the withdrawal of consent.  
During your visit to [parkcitymountain.com](http://www.parkcitymountain.com/), we will collect certain website use information for a number of purposes, namely to:

  * Make your access and shopping more convenient and efficient;
  * Establish Site activity trends;
  * Monitor Site performance; and
  * Improve Site design and functionality.

Our collection of website use information may involve the use of cookies. A cookie is a small removable data file that is stored by your browser on your computer. Cookies allow you to place an order on our website and allow us to enhance and personalize your online surfing and shopping experience. We use cookies to remember the items in your cart, recognize you when you return to our website and analyze visitor behavior.  
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookie settings. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

## How to Remove or Modify Your Personal Information

Park City Mountain Resort strives to ensure that any personal information provided and in our possession is as accurate, current and complete as necessary for the purposes for which we use that information.  
If you have signed up for an account either through joining a Park City Mountain Resort Card program or making a purchase, we have provided you with a means to log into your account and edit your personal information including name, postal address and phone number to ensure its accuracy at all times.  
Park City Mountain Resort permits access to and review of Personal Information we hold about an individual by the individual concerned or the account holder. Park City Mountain Resort reserves the right to decline access to Personal Information where the information requested:

  * Would disclose the Personal Information of another individual or of a deceased individual;
  * Would disclose business confidential information that may harm Park City Mountain Resort or the competitive position of a third party;
  * Is subject to attorney-client or litigation privilege;
  * Could reasonably result in serious harm to the treatment or recovery of the individual concerned, serious emotional harm to the individual or another individual, or serious bodily harm to another individual;
  * May harm or interfere with law enforcement activities and other investigative or regulatory functions of a body authorized by statute to perform such functions;
  * Is not readily retrievable and the burden or cost of providing would be disproportionate to the nature or value of the information; or
  * Does not exist, is not held, or cannot be found by Park City Mountain Resort.

Where information will not or cannot be disclosed, the individual making the request will be provided with the reasons for nondisclosure.  
Where information will be disclosed, we will endeavor to provide the information in question within a reasonable time and no later than 30 days following the request.  
We will not respond to repetitious or vexatious requests. In determining whether a request is repetitious or vexatious, we will consider such factors as the frequency with which information is updated, the purpose for which the information is used, and the nature of the information.  
All non-transactional emails have an unsubscribe link that can be used to discontinue them.

## Transferability

All season pass and gift cards remain the property of Park City Mountain Resort.  Lift access products, including season passes, 5 pack, 10 pack, single and multi-day tickets are not transferrable and my not be loaned or given to another person.  Use of lift access by anyone other than the person to whom it was issued is considered theft of services and is punishable by law.  Gift cards are fully transferrable.  Treat all media like cash.  Park City Mountain Resort is not responsible for use if the card is lost or stolen.  Gift cards may only be used at Park City Mountain Resort owned and operated shops/restaurants and online at parkcitymountain.com and may not be exchanged for cash.  Gift cards and season passes may be reloaded.  Please report all lost or stolen cards immediately by calling (435) 649-8111 or you may contact us at: Park City Mountain Resort Services Office, Park City Mountain Resort. Park City, UT 84060.

## Questions and Feedback

Park City Mountain Resort can be [contacted online](http://www.parkcitymountain.com/), at (435) 649-8111 or by writing to Park City Mountain, Park City Mountain Resort, PO Box 39, Park City, UT 84060  
Park City Mountain Resort owns and operates the Internet sites located at [parkcitymountain.com](http://www.parkcitymountain.com/), [saveoursnow.net](http://www.saveoursnow.net/), [irideparkcity.tv](http://www.irideparkcity.tv/) (the "Site"), on servers in the United States. By accessing, browsing and/or using the pages in this Site, you agree to these terms and conditions ("Terms and Conditions") and you attest that you are at least 18 years of age. **This agreement contains disclaimers and other provisions that limit our liability to you.** If you do not agree to these Terms and Conditions, do not access, browse or use this Site.  
Additional terms and conditions apply to functionality provided through the Site and are incorporated herein by reference.  
These terms and conditions apply to [parkcitymountain.com](http://www.parkcitymountain.com/), [saveoursnow.net](http://www.saveoursnow.net/), [irideparkcity.tv](http://www.irideparkcity.tv/) and other domains owned and operated by Park City Mountain Resort including blogs and discussion sites.  
**While we make reasonable efforts to provide accurate and timely information about Park City Mountain Resort on this Site, you should not assume that the information is always instantaneously accurate or that this Site contains all the relevant information available about Park City Mountain Resort.**

## Copyright and Trademark

Unless otherwise noted, all materials on this Site are protected as the copyrights, trademarks and/or other intellectual properties owned by Park City Mountain Resort and/or its subsidiaries and affiliates or by other parties that have licensed their material to Park City Mountain Resort.  
Park City Mountain Resort marks on this Site represent some of the marks currently owned or controlled in the United States by Park City Mountain Resort. The display of these marks and of notices associated with these marks is not intended to be a comprehensive compilation of all Park City Mountain Resort ownership rights, and Park City Mountain Resort may own or control other proprietary rights. You may not reproduce, redistribute or otherwise use any materials without the express written consent of Park City Mountain Resort. All rights not expressly granted are reserved.

## Personal Use

Your use of the materials included on this Site is for personal, informational and shopping purposes only. You agree you will not distribute, publish, transmit, modify, display or create derivative works from or exploit the contents of this Site in any way. You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless Park City Mountain Resort for any and all unauthorized uses you may make of any material on the Site. You acknowledge the unauthorized use of the contents could cause irreparable harm to Park City Mountain Resort and that in the event of an unauthorized use, Park City Mountain Resort shall be entitled to an injunction in addition to any other remedies available at law or in equity.

## Feedback and Submissions

You agree you are and shall remain solely responsible for the contents of any submissions you make, and you will not submit material that is unlawful, defamatory, abusive or obscene. You agree that you will not submit anything to the Site that will violate any right of any third party, including copyright, trademark, privacy or other personal or proprietary right(s).  
We sincerely appreciate your interest in Park City Mountain Resort. Please note that any materials submitted through [the Site](http://www.parkcitymountain.com/) or through the submission process of this Site will be deemed submitted under their respective terms and conditions.

## Product Sales and Availability

All prices displayed on the Site are quoted in U.S. Dollars and are valid and effective only in the United States. Park City Mountain Resort reserves the right without prior notice to discontinue or change specifications on products and services offered on this Site without incurring any obligations.

## Links

Some links on the Site will allow you to connect with sites that are not under our control. Park City Mountain Resort is providing these links only as a convenience. The appearance of a link does not imply Park City Mountain Resort endorsement, nor is Park City Mountain Resort responsible for the contents of any linked site. You access them at your own risk.  
**Warranty**  
Except as otherwise expressly stated with respect to our products, all contents of the Site are offered on an "as is" basis without any warranty whatsoever either expressed or implied. Park City Mountain Resort makes no representations, express or implied, including without limitation implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose.  
Park City Mountain Resort does not guarantee that the functions contained in the Site will be uninterrupted or error-free, that this Site or its server will be free of viruses or other harmful components, or that defects will be corrected _even if Park City Mountain Resort is aware of them_.

## Jurisdiction

Any dispute arising from these terms shall be resolved exclusively in the state and federal courts of the State of Utah. Park City Mountain Resort makes no representation that materials in this Site are appropriate or available for use in other locations. If you access this Site from outside the United States, be advised this Site may contain references to products and services that are not available or are prohibited in your country.

## GENERAL TERMS:

Park City Mountain Resort, Park City Mountain Resort Central Reservations, and its affiliated companies make reasonable efforts to ensure that website data is correct; however, properties, products, services, and information published on this and other related websites may include inaccuracies or typographical errors. Park City Mountain Resort and its Affiliates do not guarantee the accuracy of, and disclaim liability for inaccuracies relating to the pricing and description of the vacation rental properties, car, and other travel products displayed on this website (including, without limitation, photographs, property descriptions, amenities, pricing, etc.). Changes and improvements to descriptions and pricing may be made at any time and without notice.

The price for the hospitality package will be as quoted on the Website from time to time, except in cases of obvious error. Please note that Park City Mountain Resort Central Reservations is under no obligation to provide the hospitality package to the customer at an incorrect lower price, even after a booking confirmation has been received if the pricing error was obvious, unmistakable, and could reasonably have been recognized by the Customer as a mis-pricing error.

A hotel room is defined as a single room with a bathroom. Hotel rooms may offer different forms of bedding that typically include one of the following: king, queen, full, twin, bunk, Murphy bed, trundle, or sofa-sleeper. Hotel rooms do not typically include a kitchen, or a separate bedroom.

A studio is defined as room consisting of a main room, kitchenette, and bathroom. Studios may offer different forms of bedding that typically include one of the following: king, queen, full, twin, bunk, Murphy bed, trundle, or sofa-sleeper.

Bedding options are only meant to provide a partial list, other options may apply. 

## RENTAL TERMS:

Pets are not allowed in any of our properties unless specified in writing. All properties are non-smoking unless otherwise noted. There are no refunds for late arrivals and/or early departures. A major credit card is typically required upon check-in to cover incidental charges. Park City Mountain Resort Central Reservations reserves the right to supply client’s credit card information to unit supplier if a credit card is not given upon check-in. Specific unit numbers and bed configurations are not guaranteed. We reserve the right to provide accommodations of equal or greater value, at no extra charge, if it becomes necessary to relocate a guest or group should a property become unavailable for any reason.
